Hear the voices that power could not silence
Untouchable is a documentary film directed by Ursula Macfarlane.
The inside story of the rise and fall of Harvey Weinstein reveals how, over decades, he
acquired and protected his power even when scandal threatened to engulf him.
Former colleagues and accusers detail the method and consequences of his
alleged abuse, hoping for justice and also to inspire change.
Self, played by Rosanna Arquette.
Self, played by Hope Exiner D'Amore.
Self, played by Paz de la Huerta.
Self, played by Caitlin Dulany.
Self, played by Ronan Farrow.
Self, played by Louise Godbold.
Untouchable is a 2019 British documentary film about film producer Harvey
Weinstein and the sexual abuse allegations that involve him.
It was directed by Ursula Macfarlane.
The film explores themes of sexual abuse, biography,
hollywood, sexual assault, metoo.